http://www.automaticvalve.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policies
User Privacy Policy for ROSS Operating Valve Company, ROSS Controls®, ROSS DECCO®, and Automatic Valve Industrial, collectively the “ROSS Group”. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of the online product catalog at this site. This policy may change from time to time so please re-visit this page periodically. Web sites which are linked to this site may have different policies and the ROSS Group is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
Disclosure and Use of Information
You can visit this site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the domain names, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. In general, we gather information about users of the site collectively in order to determine, for example, which areas users access more frequently, and which materials users access the most. This information helps us to determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for our users by improving the content of this site.Any personal information you provide on this site may be used, held or shared by the ROSS Group and its affiliates, associated companies, agents, distributors or others in the supply chain to fulfill your order and provide you services associated with products you purchase through this site (together, the “ROSS organization"). The processing of personal data, such as the name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number of a data subject shall always be in line with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), and in accordance with the country-specific data protection regulations applicable to ROSS Europa GmbH.The ROSS Group does not sell, trade, loan or rent your personal information to others outside of the ROSS organization. We may disclose information in special cases when we believe in good faith that such release is necessary to comply with law, to identify or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our conditions of use and terms of service, to enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements, or protect the rights, property or safety of the ROSS Group or others. The ROSS Group is a global company and this site has users all over the world. Any information you give us through this site may be transmitted to servers outside the country where the information was entered, and may be used, stored and processed outside of the country where it was entered. We may use certain information gathered from this site to compile demographic data about our users, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. If provided to third parties, this data will include no personally identifying information.
Security
We will use every reasonable effort to ensure the security of our system and will strive to protect any personal information you provide through this site. Unfortunately, we cannot guarantee that all data transmitted over the Internet will be secure.
Registered Users
When you become a Registered User, we ask for your name, email address, and other information to assist us in processing your request. You will be asked whether you would like to receive e-mail messages regarding our products or other topics with may be of interest to you. We won't send you such messages without your consent.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server to be stored on your hard drive that allows easier access the next time the same page is visited. For example, a cookie is sent when you register or sign in to this site. This site may use cookies to store information from forms you fill out to create a user profile so that you do not have to re-enter the information each time you visit. Your browser probably can be set to notify you whenever a cookie is received so you can decide whether or not to accept it, but you will not be able to use this site if you choose not to accept cookies from us.
IP Addresses
An IP address is a number which is used to identify computers so that data such as web pages you request can be sent to you. Our web server automatically collects IP addresses for purposes of administering our system and to help us diagnose problems with our server.
Consent
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by the ROSS Group.
Website Use Policy
Your use of the Website constitutes your agreement to follow these rules and to be bound by them. If you do not agree with any of these Terms and Conditions, do not use this Website.
These Terms and Conditions May Change
The ROSS Group reserves the right to update or modify these Terms and Conditions in subsequent versions of the Website at any time without prior notice. Your use of the Website following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Terms and Conditions as changed. For this reason, we encourage you to review the Terms and Conditions whenever you use the Website.
Copyright Notice
All of the content you see or hear on this Website, including, for example, page headers, images, illustrations, graphics, audio clips, video clips, and text, are subject to trademark, service mark, trade dress, copyright and/or other intellectual property rights or licenses held the ROSS Group, one of its subsidiaries, affiliates or by third persons who have licensed their materials the ROSS Group. The entire content of this Website is copyrighted as a collective work under U.S. and international copyright laws, and the ROSS Group owns a copyright in the selection, coordination, arrangement and enhancement of the content. The content of this Website and this Website as a whole are intended solely for your use. You may download and/or transfer, print and store selected portions of the content, where the ROSS Group has provided a print/download function, provided you (a) only use these copies of the content for your own non-commercial use, e.g., product specification pages, order, acknowledgement, etc. You may not copy or post the content on any network computer or broadcast the content in any media, and you may not modify or alter the content in any way or delete or change any copyright or trademark notice. No right, title or interest in any downloaded or copied materials is transferred to you as a result of any such downloading or copying. The ROSS Group reserves complete title and full intellectual property rights in any content you download or copy from this Website. Except as noted above, you may not copy, download, reproduce, modify, publish, distribute, transmit, transfer or create derivative works from the content without first obtaining written permission from the ROSS Group.
Submissions
We welcome your comments regarding this Website. However, any comments, feedback, notes, messages, ideas, suggestions or other communications ("Comments") sent to us via any medium shall be and remain the exclusive property of the ROSS Group. Your submission shall constitute an assignment to the ROSS Group of all worldwide rights, titles and interests in all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in the Comments. The ROSS Group shall be entitled to use, reproduce, disclose, publish and distribute any materials you submit for any purpose whatsoever, without restriction and without compensating you in any way. For this reason, do not send any Comments that you do not wish to assign to us, including any confidential information or any original creative materials such as stories, product ideas, computer code or original artwork.
Correction of Errors and Inaccuracies
The information on this Website may contain typographical errors or inaccuracies and may not be complete or current. We therefore reserve the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update information at any time without prior notice (including after you have submitted a request for quote or order). Please note that such errors, inaccuracies or omissions may relate to product descriptions, specifications, technical information, dimensions, sizing, pricing and availability. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you. Regional Quotes and Product Availability Requests for quote and purchase requests to addresses outside the United States cannot be filled by our U. S. affiliate(s) but will be forwarded to the appropriate regional affiliate(s) for quotation and/or sale. Products described in this Website may not be available in your region. We do not claim that the information in the Website is appropriate to your jurisdiction or that the products described in this Website will be available for purchase in all jurisdictions.
Disclaimers
THE ROSS GROUP WEBSITES ARE OPERATED BY ROSS CONTROLS ON AN "AS IS", "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS, WITHOUT REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. THE ROSS GROUP, AND ITS SUBSIDIARIES AND AFFILIATES ("ROSS BUSINESSES") DISCLAIM ANY AND ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES WITH RESPECT TO THIS WEBSITE AND ITS CONTENTS, WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.
THE ROSS GROUP DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, FOR ANY MERCHANDISE OFFERED ON THIS WEBSITE.
THE ROSS GROUP DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE OR CURRENT OR THAT THIS WEBSITE WILL OPERATE WITHOUT INTERRUPTION OR ERROR.
THE ROSS GROUP DOES NOT CLAIM THAT THE INFORMATION IN THE WEBSITE IS APPROPRIATE TO YOUR JURISDICTION OR THAT THE PRODUCTS DESCRIBED IN THIS WEBSITE WILL BE AVAILABLE FOR PURCHASE IN ALL JURISDICTIONS.
THE ROSS GROUP DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY AS TO THE ACCURACY OR COMPLETENESS OF EACH ITEM'S DESCRIPTION, SPECIFICATION, TECHNICAL INFORMATION, DIMENSIONING AND SIZING. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO VERIFY ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS WEBSITE BEFORE RELYING UPON IT.
THE ROSS GROUP DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THIS WEBSITE IS FREE OF COMPUTER VIRUSES, BUGS OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS.
THE ROSS GROUP DOES NOT ENDORSE NOR MAKE ANY WARRANTIES, RECOMMENDATIONS OR REPRESENTATIONS ABOUT ANY OTHER WEB SITE YOU MAY ACCESS THROUGH A ROSS GROUP WEBSITE. LINKS TO WEB SITES ARE PROVIDED FOR CONVENIENCE ONLY. YOU NEED TO MAKE YOUR OWN DECISIONS REGARDING YOUR INTERACTIONS OR COMMUNICATIONS WITH ANY OTHER WEB SITE.
IF ANY PART OF THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ARE DETERMINED TO BE INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE, THEN THE INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE PROVISION WILL BE DEEMED SUPERsEDED BY A VALID, ENFORCEABLE PROVISION THAT MOST CLOSELY MATCHES THE INTENT OF THE ORIGINAL PROVISION AND THE REMAINING TERMS AND CONDITIONS SHALL CONTINUE IN EFFECT.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL THE ROSS GROUP OR ANY OF THEIR EMPLOYEES, DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, AGENTS, VENDORS OR SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT LOSSES OR DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEBSITE. THIS IS A COMPREHENSIVE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY THAT APPLIES TO ALL LOSSES AND DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (WHETHER GENERAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, PUNITIVE OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION, LOSS OF DATA, INCOME OR PROFITS), WHETHER IN CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, EVEN IF AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF ANY ROSS BUSINESS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THE ROSS WEBSITE OR ANY CONTENT OF THE WEBSITE, OR WITH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THE WEBSITE. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE, BY YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE, THAT YOU ARE USING THIS WEBSITE AT YOUR OWN AND SOLE RISK. APPLICABLE LAW MAY NOT ALLOW THE LIMITATION OF LIABILITY SET FORTH ABOVE, SO THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. THE INVALIDITY OF ANY TERM, CONDITION OR PROVISION SHALL NOT AFFECT THE ENFORCEABILITY OF THOSE PORTIONS DEEMED ENFORCEABLE BY APPLICABLE COURTS OF LAW. IF ANY PART OF THIS LIMITATION ON LIABILITY IS FOUND TO BE INVALID OR UNENFORCEABLE FOR ANY REASON, THEN THE AGGREGATE LIABILITY OF ROSS BUSINESSES UNDER SUCH CIRCUMSTANCES FOR LIABILITIES THAT OTHERWISE WOULD HAVE BEEN LIMITED SHALL NOT EXCEED ONE HUNDRED DOLLARS ($100). ENFORCEMENT, APPLICABLE LAW and JURISDICTION.By accessing and using a ROSS Group Website, you agree that your access to and use of it is subject to these terms and conditions, as well as all applicable laws, as governed and interpreted pursuant to the LAWS OF THE STATE OF MICHIGAN, U.S.A. You hereby consent to the EXCLUSIVE JURISDICTION AND VENUE of the courts in OAKLAND COUNTY, MICHIGAN, U.S.A. in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of this Website. Use is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these terms and conditions, including this paragraph.
